[Episode 5]
Can I help you?
Yes, thanks. I wonder if we could borrow some...
Who are you?
Can't you recognize your mother and sister?
Why are you guys staring at me?
Is there something on my face?
There is. No joking, lots of stuff on your face.
Alright, alright! I already made a promise.
Today at five, at the Seoul Hotel
first floor coffee shop... A guy...
He works at Dongseong Trade,
has an 80-square-meter apartment in Gangnam,
and his bank account...
- Who?
- Your date.
I'm set up for a blind date, mom?
Alright, alright.
If this date gets cancelled,
I'm going to dig a hole and bury myself.
There's a lot riding on this!
It's not a threat.
Mom looked at coffins a while ago.
I looked at a blackish copper coffin.
Give it up, mom.
This doesn't have the slightest chance of happening.
If Eunchae goes on this date then
I'll immediately go into Seoul University.
Well yeah. If Eunchae goes...
Then I'll give you this bed, mom.
Yeah. If she goes on this date,
you'll be her mother.
I'll go on the date.
With news as good as that,
you should have told me sooner.
If I fall for him at first sight,
can I propose to him first, mom?
Do you not like me?
It's not that I don't like you.
You're just not my type.
What is your type?
It's hard for me to say...
Do you want to draw your type then?
Ten minutes haven't even passed.
How can you tell if I'm your type or not?
If you take a closer look, I might be your type.
I can tell in one minute.
How do you figure that out in a minute, huh? Nonsense.
I can.
- It doesn't make sense.
- Why not?
- It doesn't
- It does!
Tell me the truth.
What exactly don't you like about me?
How can I say it directly?
Tell me. It's alright.
Geez.
Since you're so insistent...
I really don't like how you look. Happy now?
What about how I look?
Geez.
Take a look in the mirror.
Let's split the bill.
I've got to go to the studio.
I don't think I can drive you.
It's okay. That's why I brought my car.
I'll call you. Get home safe.
How can I help you?
Hey!
Lady! Get out.
"Lady"?
You... Where do you look when driving?
Look here, guy.
Lady, my baby is stuck beneath your car.
Huh?
Oh my god!
Move your car.
Didn't you hear me?
I didn't know.
When I was parking, I didn't feel a thing.
Move the car.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. I'll pay you.
If this isn't enough, leave me with your number.
You know who I am right? I'm Kang Minj?
What is this?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you trying to hit on me?
Well, you picked the wrong person, man.
I'm Kang Minju! You can't be like this.
Shut up and move your car.
You have one minute to get lost.
Choi Yun!
Hi man. Where were you?
Where are you?
The studio. Wanna come over?
Am I officially your manager from today?
Yeah, work officially starts tomorrow.
Wait ten minutes.
I just got in a taxi... I'll be there soon.
What a poor, little puppy.
I'll wash you up clean.
So you're not crazy.
Fine then. Let's date.
Am I a joke to you? Do I look like a pushover?
If you show up again, you're dead meat!
Why is that sound coming all the way through here?
Sangchae, wake up!
Oh my. There is a photoshoot today, right?
Yun. Son.
Wake up and wash and then
let's get to the photoshoot.
Not waking up?
Get up, get up!
Hurry and get up, get up!
Just date your son, why don't you?
Disgusting!
Do you have a telephone pole stuck up your ears?
I may have given birth to you
but you guys are pathetic!
Audrey, birth name Jo Malbok.
You're so full of yourself because of
your oh-so-great son.
But I might just have Eunchae seduce him.
This headache of yours might just
give you a daughter-in-law!
Fire!
Samchae! Fire!
Stop joking around.
Are you up?
I have been for a while.
Then why pretend to be asleep?
Just because.
I didn't want to open my eyes,
so I just lazily stayed put.
Yun and his mother have a photo shoot
outside the city today.
Yeah.
Are you sick?
Look at this sweat.
You even have a fever!
I'm a little sick, I guess.
Do you think you can go?
You're normally like steel.
It's okay. I'll get better.
Hello, doggy dog. Sleep well?
Did you have a good night's sleep?
Yes. Good morning.
Wake up Yun. I can't do a thing to wake him up.
He's still sleeping?
Yeah, he went to sleep late.
He said he dreamed of a ghost.
He even came into my room and slept with me.
Okay.
- Oh, Eunchae.
- Yes?
Don't tell Minju about Yun being this way.
Being what way?
Like not being able to sleep alone after a scary dream,
or how he's afraid of ghosts at his age.
Sure. I won't tell her.
Yun, wake up! You have a shoot to go to.
Wake up, it's late.
People are waiting for you. Are you going to cancel?
I'm going to cancel.
Wake up. Oh, good boy!
I'm not good!
You know about the Kong Kong Ghost right?
The ghost who died falling upside-down
from a three story building?
The ghost who walks on its head.
It sounds like "kong kong kong."
The kong kong ghost is searching for the person
who pushed her to her death.
The pusher's name is Choi Yun.
Kong kong kong.
It just opened the door and entered.
It's gotten into the living room...
Kong kong kong.
It goes up the stairs...
Has it reached Yun's room?
He's not in here...
Kong kong kong.
Then after that, it goes back downstairs...
Finds out...
that Yun is in his mom's room.
Kong kong kong.
There is something laying down by your side.
Sleep well with the kong kong ghost. I'm off.
Hey!
- Yun!
- Yes?
Why don't you get off of me and go?
Let go.
No.
Hey, am I your wife? Am I your mother?
Why are you being so gross?
What?
What did you just say? I'm gross?
Yes, you are.
That makes me depressed, Eunchae!
Really depressed.
I'm not going to the shoot today.
Do whatever you want.
Is she on drugs?
I should emigrate.
Go and live away for ten years and come back.
Am I really that sick?
Get yourself together, Eunchae!
Get yourself together.
Why did you poke me?
So it is you.
Why poke me?
I thought I was hallucinating and wanted to check...
- Do you like me too?
- No!
Then why poke a man minding his own business?
You do you like me, right? So that's why you poked me.
No!
Your face isn't looking well. You sick somewhere?
No.
- You look sick.
- No.
- Your face is pale.
- No!
- Is no the only thing you can say?
- No.
- You hate me, right?
- No...
Am I a joke to you?
Do I look like a pushover?
If you show up again, you're dead meat!
You stupid blockhead.
Hey!
I warned you, didn't I?
That if you showed up again, I'd kill you?
I do what I say. If I say I'll kill you, I do it.
Kill me.
Hey.
You are crazy, huh?
- Are you a pervert?
- Yeah.
Go. Just go.
Go back to your country.
Go back to Australia.
Go, I said go.
I don't like you. You're seriously not my type.
I don't even like thinking about guys
like you, so leave.
Leave, please!
What are you doing, Eunchae?
Who are you to tell my bro to go or not?
Sleep well?
You sleep well too, bro? When'd you get here?
An hour ago.
I have a photo shoot with my mom today.
Let's leave together when she comes out.
Sure.
This man... The new manager is this man?
That's right, why?
Are you nuts? Are you crazy?
How can you hire a jerk like him?
How can you talk like that? "A jerk like him?"
He's older than you are. And...
Are you on drugs today?
From now on, I'm no longer your coordinator.
Hire someone else.
Sorry, sorry, sorry. We're late because of me, right?
Mom, Eunchae says she won't
be my coordinator anymore.
Why?
I don't know. She says I should hire someone else.
Why, Eunchae? Did Yun do something wrong again?
How could he hire anyone else?
No one can handle Yun but you.
They'd have to go to Mars to find someone else.
It's not that.
I'll scold Yun later.
Lets go right now. We're late. Lets go.
You?
He became my manager yesterday, mom.
You know Muhyeok, right?
It must be that time of the month for Eunchae.
Yun...
She's being a weird brat. She says I'm disgusting.
And a while ago, she swore at Muhyeok,
calling him a jerk.
She's crossing the line, that girl.
She is a grown woman. Don't call her "girl."
Eunchae, did you get this guy a job?
No. No, ma'am.
Isn't he your boyfriend, Eunchae?
No, it's nothing like that.
Eunchae, if you ask me who I'd choose
between Muhyeok and you,
I'd choose Muhyeok no matter what.
Got that?
Why? Because Muhyeok is cool! He's not a snob like you.
Son!
If anyone badmouths him again,
they'll get it from me, no matter who. Got it?
I'm being petty, huh?
"Who does he think he is?"
I'm immature, dirty, and nauseating.
And petty. And disgusting, right?
You should at least say something.
- Yun.
- What?
Let's end things with no hard feelings.
What?
It's our last day, so I want to end it nicely.
- Are you really going to quit?
- Yes.
Hey.
I am going to quit. Today is my last day.
- Eunchae, you finish things up.
- Yes, ma'am.
Mother, Eunchae is really going to quit today.
Son...
If you were to ask me to choose between
Eunchae and that Muhyeok guy or whoever,
I'd pick Eunchae no matter what.
What is wrong with everyone?
I don't like that guy either.
Why? What don't you like about him?
I just don't.
I don't like him. So cut the stubbornness.
But he's a really cool guy. You don't even know him.
Eunchae, I'm going to fire him no matter what.
So you stay with Yun, okay?
Mister!
Pervert!
This sky isn't that great.
The Australian sky is beautiful.
Our country's sky is pretty too.
Australia's is prettier.
Then go back to Australia.
If it's that pretty, go to your country
and live happily.
Traitor.
How would it feel to be up there?
Would it look much better than it does from here?
If you're so curious, then why don't you go?
I am going.
I'll be going there soon.
Yes, ma'am?
You're finished?
I'm close by. I'll be there soon.
Yes, ma'am.
They're eating after the photo shoot.
They're eating!
Aren't you going to eat?
If you're getting fired anyway...
Do you have money to buy a plane ticket?
Want me to buy it for you?
Yun is going to fire you. That's what was decided.
I guess it's better this way.
Instead of wearing yourself out about it,
It's better to not start something
that isn't meant to happen.
So... I'm not saying that it's happened to me before.
But from my experience...
Before we're too close and
before emotions get too deep,
we should just end it quick.
That way, we won't be hurt and
it'll be easier to forget...
Mister!
Welcome!
This is the only place that's opened.
I'll buy you something nice when we go back to Seoul.
Well, nothing we can about that.
Come sit here.
Excuse me!
What'll you have?
- I'll have beef rib soup.
- I'll have beef soup.
Our place has blood sausage and blood sausage soup.
Would you like blood sausage?
Sure, just give us those then.
Then why even ask us?
My stomach... I'll go to the restroom.
Where's the restroom?
Go straight... and then that way...
And from there go that way...
and go straight and there it is.
Where did that lady say it is?
I don't know either.
How can she put her finger in the soup and serve it?
Let's just eat it, ma'am.
- It's quite good.
- It's good.
It's disgusting and dirty. How can you eat this?
It's here.
What is that? That's cow blood, right?
I can't eat this.
Just try some. It's really good.
I've lost my appetite. I can't eat this stuff.
This is what savages eat. Get it away from me.
You eat all of it.
It's not for eating, it's for throwing on you.
I should douse you with this soup!
Eunchae! Yun! Yun! My Yun!
Get back.
Be quiet!
Quiet!
[Jeong Huisu]
Jang Haesuk!
[Kim Kyeong-eun]
Kim Kangwoo... You two!
Oh... The stench!
I don't think I can do this here.
Hello?
Huh? What happened to my mother?
I won't do anything! Let go!
Don't, Eunchae. I want Yun to see all of this.
Please calm down, ma'am.
No. I can't!
You! You messed with the wrong person today.
Your business is over, lady!
I'm going to tell my son and have this place torn down
and have a new building built on top of it.
What the heck is she blabbing about?
Let go! Let go!
- Mom!
- Yun!
What happened to your face?
That lady... She poured that dirty food,
that blood all over my face.
What did you do, mom?
What do you mean what did I do?
I only said I can't eat the food
because it's not my liking,
yet she did this to me!
I'm so angry and feel so wronged!
Look at her now trying to pour that on me again.
This is the first time I've ever dealt with this.
I'm so wronged I just want to die, Yun.
[Together Forever]
Son! Son!
Son!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Have you gone insane? Stop!
Head back first, ma'am.
Why? What about you?
I need to stop by somewhere.
Stop by where? Do you know any place around here?
I have a friend who lives nearby. Head back first.
What friend?
I know every one of your friends.
Not this one.
I'll see you in Seoul, ma'am.
If they were adopted at that time...
These should be the babies.
Can you make a copy of this for me?
Excuse me?
How may I help you?
I just have some questions to ask.
Does a Yun Seo-kyeong reside here?
Yun Seo-kyeong?
Yes, Yun Seo-kyeong.
Oh that girl.
She lived here for quite a while,
but she moved a few months ago.
Moved?
Yes. Why are you looking for her?
It's nothing. Excuse me.
What's the difference between Jjangoo and an octopus?
Jjangoo and an octopus? What is the difference?
Jjangoo...
Well, Jjangoo...
Jjangoo can't be caught while an octopus can be.
Oh, that's true.
It is, isn't it?
You didn't have to go that far. You overreacted.
We didn't have to go that far.
That's why we paid them for the damage.
Money isn't everything.
Ah, I know now why Eunchae stayed behind.
Why?
The soup place.
She probably went to that lady.
She'd go there... I'm sure of it.
Ma'am. Have a seat. I'll clean it for you.
What are you doing?
Just have a seat, ma'am.
Turn around. A while ago, it seemed you hurt your back.
I'll put a patch on it.
Actually, would you rather go to the hospital with me?
I'm tired. Mom, I wanna sleep.
Okay. Sleep, my son.
Were you alarmed? I'm sorry for that. It was my fault.
It's okay. Sing me a lullaby.
Okay.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm in front of the house.
We will be arriving very soon.
Yun is sleeping.
Alright, see you later.
Yun. Wake up!
Son, wake up. We're home.
Huh? Minju!
Have fun?
I missed you so much I thought I was going to die.
Me too! Have a good time?
Yeah.
You can go home now. You did a good job.
I'll call you.
Let's go in.
Is he your new manager?
Yeah. But not after tomorrow.
- That won't be necessary, Yun.
- Huh?
I want to keep him for now.
As you said, he might be an okay guy.
I'll try to assure Eunchae about it.
I'm hungry. Make me something good, son.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
Have you gone insane? Stop!
Are you okay?
Did the train to Seoul leave?
It left.
[Inn]
Ma'am!
Yes?
Where's my wife?
She's in there.
Open up!
[My Eunchae]
Recipient is not answering.
Where is this girl?
[Medicine Packet]
Lady! Get out.
You... live here?
We've met before, right?
You must be the new guy that moved in downstairs.
What a small world, huh?
All the better. That day was crazy.
If it's alright with you,
I'd like to buy you a new dog.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you hitting on me?
You got the wrong person, lady.
Hey!
How do people like that exist?
Seo-kyeong. Why are you sleeping here?
Why the floor and not the bed?
Sleep comfortably on the bed.
I told you to sleep on the bed!
Mommy...
How long do you intend to live this way?
You want to live the rest of your life
stuck in a tiny place like that?
Now you can live like a proper person...
On a nice bed, wearing nice clothes, eating good food!
I, your brother, am giving this life to you.
Why are you driving me crazy?
Mommy...
Shut up! Quiet!
What did Mom do for you that you'd call her?
Where's mother? Where is a mother for us?
Mother...
Shut up! Be quiet, you idiot!
My mother is not an idiot.
Galchi...
- Mom...
- Galchi...
Did you hit my mother?
Galchi, let's go back to our home.
Okay... Okay.
Let's go home.
Let's go home, mom.
Let's go, mom.
Who was it?
Was it Yun?
Why don't just you kill me, you brat?
Just worry me to death!
Friend? Yeah right.
You went to the soup place, right? I just know it.
I mean, Muhyeok caused the damage,
so why did you settle things?
Do you have that much strength?
You look like a light breeze
would knock you over.
Look at you looking all gaunt.
Yun...
I stayed up all night because of you. You know that?
I do.
What do you know?
I thought it was you.
What?
I knew you were the one
taking care of me all night.
What are you talking about?
Thank you, Yun.
I'm really really thankful.
If not for you, I...
I would have died.
Thank you for saving my life, Yun.
Hey, why are you crying all of sudden?
For not knowing your heart,
and for getting angry at you...
I'm so sorry, Yun.
For being mean to you... and making you sad...
I'm so sorry.
No, I'm more sorry, actually.
I was wrong, Eunchae.
I won't do that again...
Me too... I won't do that again too.
[Episode 6 Preview]
You're like a sloppy child
with food on your face.
Get out of my face, you brats!
You're so pretty, my sister.
What will I do if Minju dumps me?
Then I'm going to kill myself.
Die then.
Are you Song Eunchae? Please let us interview you.
Are the news reports about your relationship true?